別 求你了
等下 別!
等等 不要!
- 嘿 Hotch在哪?  - 在開預算會議
- Hey,where's hotch? - Budget meeting.
也許他會給我們爭取到預算增加
Maybe he'll get us a raise.
上頭巴不得減預算呢 怎麼會加錢 只希望別省了咖啡錢
They're cutting, not raising. I just hope they don't take the coffee.
- 那我不幹了 - 行啊 你不幹 每周省50塊給我
- I'd quit. - Oh,yeah. That'll save 'em like 50 bucks a week.
- 他會在飛機上跟我們碰頭  - 我們去哪?
- He'll meet us on the plane. - Where are we going?
昨晚 警長辦公室門口  發現3個被斬首的人頭
Last night, 3 decapitated heads were found in front of a sheriff's station
在德克薩斯州的一個邊陲小鎮Terlingua
in the small border town of terlingua,texas.
一次發現三個受害人?
3 victims at once?
其實 三人的屍首腐爛程度不同
Actually,they appear to be in different stages of decomposition.
驗屍證實 其中一個人頭剛被砍下一天左右
M.e.confirmed that one of the heads is a day or so old.
其他兩人似乎死於幾個月前
The other 2 appear to have died a few months ago,
但傷口砍痕顯示他們是最近被斬首
But the wound edges suggest that they were decapitated recently.
口 耳 鼻均有泥土
Dirt in their mouth, ears,and nose.
- 表明這兩個頭被埋過 - 然後又被挖出來
- At some point, these two heads were buried. - And then dug up.
好的 那為何又突然挖出他們?
Ok,so why the sudden need to display them?
可能並不是突然需要挖出
The need may not be so sudden.
墨西哥 僅2009年一年 就發現10個被斬首的人頭
Mexico,in 2009 alone, 10 heads in coolers,
而這些人頭所屬的受害者 都是發現前幾小時才被殺
And the people belonging to these heads we're killed just hours before they were found.
販毒集團幫派爭鬥的結果
Result of a battle between feuding drug cartels.
DEA(違禁藥品緝查局)不感興趣嗎?
Dea's not interested?
他們說讓我們先看看
They asked us to take a look at it.
考慮到屍首腐爛程度不同 說可能無關毒品
Considering the different decomposition, this might not even be about drugs.
我們有什麼線索?
Then what do we have?
受害者是兩名男性 一名女性  所以沒有性別偏好
Well,the victims are two males,one female, so no gender preference.
在警長辦公室門口拋下斬首的頭顱 這是侵略性的表示
Staging the heads in front of a sheriff's station-- that's aggressive.
- 3名受害者均為拉美裔  - 身份不明
- All 3 victims are hispanic. - And unidentified.
Terlingua的非法"盲流"很多
Terlingua has a large illegal population.
取證這些受害者的身份非常困難
It's made i.d.ing the victims that much harder.
兇手可能試圖發出某種類型的政治聲明
He might be trying to make some type of political statement.
那堛疑銋狳腋犑蚅@者 分擔了警察很多工作
Volunteer border patrols do a lot of personal policing down there.
民兵等團體認為維持治安高於一切
Groups like the minutemen prize law and order above everything else.
這些巡邏是他們的政治議程
And those patrols serve their political agenda.
謀殺會破壞他們的形象
Murder would be bad for their image.
拋屍首在警站門口 表明不明嫌犯很可能是當地人
Staging the heads in front of a police station suggests that the unsub might be local.
他必須掌握詳細的情況 才能不被人看見
He'd have to have a knowledge about how to do something like that without being seen.
我們要面對的是 數百英里未列入轄區的沙漠
So what we have is hundreds of miles of unincorporated desert
以及龐大的每天偷越境的偷渡群
And an endless supply of anonymous victims crossing the border every day.
這是連環殺手的完美殺戮風暴
It's a serial killer's perfect storm.
犯罪心理 第五季 第19集
Criminal Minds Season05 Episode19 Rite of Passage
"只有飢餓的時候 獅子才會出動捕獵"
"a lion's work hours are only when he's hungry.
"一旦飽腹 捕食者與獵物也就和平共處"
"once he's satisfied, the predator and prey live peacefully together."
Chuck Jones (美國動畫大師 編劇 製片人)
Chuck jones.
給我解釋一下這個
Explain this to me.
不明嫌犯在美墨邊境地區找尋目標
The unsub hunts along the u.s.-mexico border.
這地有多大?
How big is that area?
5000多平方英里的沙漠
Over 5,000 square miles of desert.
他很可能行兇多年一直未被發現
He could have gone undetected for years.
- 為什麼現在要暴露自己?  - 最近一定發生了什麼事
- So why announce himself? - Something happened recently.
關於Terlingua的犯罪情況 我們知道些什麼?
What do we know about crime in terlingua?
這是一個暫居城鎮
It's a stop-over town.
移民入境會在此停留24小時 然後再進入美國
Immigrants stay only 24 hours before moving on,
但這也使該鎮成為販毒中心
but that also makes them narco-trafficking hubs.
除了違反移民法之外 大部分是跟毒品有關的逮捕案
Outside of immigration violations, most of the arrests are drug related.
美人兒 你可是輕描淡寫了
That,my pretties, in an understatement.
有人熟悉下加州的Lugo販毒集團嗎? (下加州: 墨西哥最北最西的州)
Anyone familiar with the lugo cartel out of baja california?
他們跟兩大罪惡脫不了干係 (hit也有毒品計量的意思)
Their greatest hits-- the pun being inescapable--
1990-2009間 犯下多起殘忍謀殺 以及進口分銷
Include multiple brutal murders along with importing and distributing nearly 2 tons of cocaine
近2噸的可卡因 和大量海洛因
And copious amounts of heroin between 1990 and 2009.
弱我們登上BAU的"時間機器"來到當下 便會發現一種超級便宜 更容易上癮
Now,if we get in our bau time machine, flash forward to now, a super cheap, highly addictive,
從黑焦油海洛因提煉出的不純毒品 剛在Terlingua的大街小巷上市
And totally impure form of black tar heroin just showed up on the streets of terlingua,
而DEA認為 Lugo販毒集團應為此事負責
And the dea thinks the lugo cartel is directly responsible.
他們正在拓展他們的生意
So they're expanding their operation.
而這往往會掀起腥風血浪
Which is often announced by a wave of violence.
Lugo集團去年殺了兩個DEA的探員
The lugo cartel killed 2 dea agents last year.
我們必須加倍小心
We're going to need to watch our backs.
對於販毒集團 FBI是他們的死對頭 甚至還會設立獎賞 所以...
To cartels, feds are fair game. There's even usually a bounty,so...
我們得隨身帶著這些大"玩具"
We're going to bring in the toys.
小心 我可不想在預算上增加 維修MP5槍的費用
Be careful with those. I don't need broken mp-5s on our budget.
各位 問個問題
Guys,here's the thing.
我好像沒被授權 攜帶此類武器
I don't think i technically have authorization to carry a weapon like that.
- 你沒有 - 你沒有
- You don't. - You don't.
我們這次面對的受害者群體 都不會情願和我們交談
You know,we're going to have a victim pool that is extremely hesitant to talk to us.
Prentiss 你和Morgan從移民社區入手 看能造成多大反響
Prentiss,you and morgan start with the migrant community, see what inroads you can make.
強調我們只是為了找出兇手
Stress that we're only there to catch a killer.
Rossi和Reid 驗屍官等著帶你們去看頭顱
Rossi and reid, the m.e.is waiting to show you the heads.
也許它們能給我們透點線索
Maybe they can tell us something.
德州 Terlingua
怎麼回事?
What's this about?
這是Lugo集團的一部分
This is part of the lugo cartel.
借過
Excuse us.
聯邦探員 請讓開
Federal agents. Step aside.
我們是這個國家的合法公民 在行使 憲法第一修正案賦予的和平集會的權利
We're legal citizens of this country demonstrating our first amendment rights to a peaceful assembly,
來抗議當局非法逮捕Omar Morales
In order to protest the unlawful arrest of omar morales.
請繞道而行
You walk around us.
警探們 Ruiz警長在堶惜[候  忽略這幫人
Agents,sheriff ruiz is waiting inside. Ignore them.
別幹傻事 警察同學
Don't do nothin' stupid,deputies.
你啥時候想動手 Jose  你知道去哪塈銣畯
Anytime you want to make a move,jose, you know where to find us.
你們都知道
All y'all do.
很抱歉 門口的"迎賓小組"
Sorry about the welcoming committee.
還以為你們半小時後才到
We didn't expect you for another half hour.
有多少 呃 警局埵@有幾個警察?
How many,uh, how many officers in the whole department?
包括警長的話 5個
Including the sheriff,5.
門口有8個大漢
There are 8 men outside.
這就是他們的目的 對吧? 拿人數來唬你們
And that's the point,right? To show that they outnumber you.
是啊 如果按人頭算 我們毫無勝券
Well,if it came down to numbers, we wouldn't stand a chance.
那些個混混只是為Omar Morales 賣命的士兵的零頭
Those scumbags are only a handful of the soldiers who work for omar morales.
他是當地毒品交易的樞紐點
He's the head of a local narco traffic ring.
我們今早在鎮外把他逮捕的
We picked him up this morning just outside of town.
他正往飛機場去
He was headed for the airport.
他錄口供了嗎?
Has he made a statement?
- 不好說 - 什麼意思?
- Not exactly. - Meaning?
Ruiz警長不讓我們進去問話
Sheriff ruiz won't let us talk to him.
- 為什麼? - 也許你該親自問問她
- And why is that? - Well,maybe you can ask her why.
這邊請
Right this way.
FBI到了
Fbi's here.
Eva Ruiz 很高興你們能來
Eva ruiz. I'm glad you could make it.
Hotchner探員 這位是Jareau探員
Agent hotchner. This is agent jareau.
- 要喝點什麼嗎? 咖啡? - 不用了 謝謝
- Can i get you anything? Coffee? - No,thank you.
長官 你打算怎麼對付外面的小軍隊?
Ma'am,how do you plan on dealing with the small army outside?
我計劃忽略他們
I plan on ignoring them.
- 我們可以... - 他們會站得又熱又累 然後自己走掉
- Well,we can have some of-- - they'll get hot and tired and go away on their own.
我並不擔心他們
They're the least of my worries.
- 聽說你抓了個人 - 我的手下抓的
- We heard you made an arrest. - My deputies did.
- 你不贊成? - 因為他們做錯了
- But you don't agree? - Because they're wrong.
把頭顱擺在你局門口的人  想給你傳條信息
Whoever staged these heads in front of your office is trying to tell you something.
- 他們想讓我收手 - 收手什麼?
- They want me to butt out. - Of what,exactly?
我數過 我做警長的半年來 有超過20個移民失蹤
I count more than 20 missing immigrants just in the 6 months i've been sheriff.
- 每月不止3個 - 幾乎每周一個
- That's more than 3 in a month. - Almost one victim a week.
這堨u有名字和粗略的介紹 有其他書面材料嗎?
These are just names and cursory descriptions. Is there any other paperwork?
有進行調查嗎?
Has there been any investigation?
沒人會來報案
No one will make an official report,
但我相信 這邊有人長時間行兇
But i believe somebody around here has been killing for a long time.
想笑嗎? 我離開北布魯克林 那邊的兇殺案開始減少
Want a laugh? I left brooklyn north homicide to slow down.
我為自己的半退休選錯了地點
I picked the wrong part of the country to semi-retire.
這地方亂了套
This place is swimming in dysfunction.
壓根是倖存者遊戲 沒人可信
It's a game of survival, and i can't trust anyone.
長官 你有4名警員
Ma'am,you've got 4 deputies.
我清楚地告訴他們 不要惹Omar Morales
Who i expressly told to leave omar morales alone.
看他們是怎麼執行我的命令的
You can see how well they follow orders.
你確定不是Lugo集團所為?
Then you're sure this isn't the lugo cartel?
用謀殺來傳口信  正是這些人交流的風格
Murder to send a message is the way these guys communicate.
跟我來
Come with me.
知道嗎 和普遍觀念相反 斬首並不輕鬆
You know,contrary to popular belief, decapitation is not that easy.
普遍和斬首在同一句子 還真不常見
You don't often hear popular and decapitation in the same sentence.
必須從脊柱最薄弱的地方下手
You need to strike on the weakest point of the spine.
通常在C3和C7脊椎骨之間
It's normally between the c3 and c7 vertebrae.
這埵釵h處落刀點 但每刀都砍得利落
There are multiple strikes, but they don't show any hesitation.
我知道你沒啥好解剖的  但除了表面現象外
I realize you didn't have much to work with here, but outside of the obvious,
受害者們有什麼不尋常之處嗎?
Was there anything unusual about these victims?
第二名受害者好像是盲人 如果不全瞎的話
Well,the second victim appeared to have been blind, if not completely,
也有嚴重的白內障 行動都有困難
Then he had cataracts bad enough that it was difficult for him to get around.
- 另外2人呢? - 沒這情況
- What about the other two? - No.
最近一位受害者相對年長 第一位女性受害者也較年長
The most recent victim is older. So is the first one, the woman.
我只有牙齒能做比對
Well,i only had their teeth to go by,
需要點時間才能算出準確年齡 但 是的 我同意 他們相對年長
So it would take some time to get an accurate age, but,yeah,i'd agree. They were older.
我們要找的是 所謂的個性簽名
We're looking for something that we call a signature.
所有受害者共有的特性 身體上的記號 死後才顯現的
Something that all the victims shared, some physical mark, something postmortem.
不知道這是不是你們要找的
Well,i don't know if this is what you mean,
他們的鼻子和喉嚨堻ㄕ釣F子殘渣
But they all had sand residue in their noses and throats.
- 會不會是掩埋的時候留下的? - 有可能
- Could that be from being buried? - Possibly.
但是氣管和鼻腔 有撕裂痕跡
But the trachea and the nasal passage, they were kind of torn up.
如果能看到他們的肺 我猜堶惜]滿是沙子
If i had the lungs here, i'd guess that they were full of sand as well.
像是在沙子堜I吸?
You mean like they breathed in sand?
呼吸猛烈到撕裂他們的腔管
Forcefully enough that it lacerated the passages.
他們在奔跑
They were running.
這位是FBI的Hotchner探員
This is agent hotchner from the fbi.
體面的西裝
Nice suit.
知道那傢伙帶來了多少痛苦嗎?
You know how much misery that guy is responsible for?
我是聽說過販毒集團的殘忍勾當
Yeah,i've heard some of the things this cartel's capable of.
你上司要跟他談?
Your boss gonna talk to him?
他會試試看
He's gonna try.
祝他好運
Good luck.
這要傳達什麼信息?
What kind of message is this?
可笑嗎?
It's funny?
有點
Kind of,yeah.
如果發現有競爭對手了 你們就下此毒手嗎?
A competitor moves in on your business, is that what you would do?
- 假設? - 是的
- Hypothetically? - Yeah.
我會把他開膛破肚 把內臟留給動物享用
I'd gut him from crotch to chin, then leave his intestines open for the animals,
把他的左手寄給他老婆 眼睛寄給他媽
After i sent his left hand to his wife, his eyes to his mother,
給他孩子寄舌頭 再留張紙條 說爸爸死的時候嚇得尿褲子了
And his tongue to his kids, with a note saying that their papa had died wetting himself.
是個懦夫
A coward.
就算假設來說 這個也不叫信息
This,this ain't no message. Hypothetically.
這個辯解很有趣 說你下手會更狠
That's an interesting defense, saying that you would do worse.
辯解? 是你問了我問題
A defense? You asked me a question.
要是覺得我需要辯解 那就起訴我
You think i need a defense, charge me with something.
昨晚留在警局門外的那些頭 你怎麼看?
What do you know about the heads that were left outside the sheriff's station last night?
- 說真的? - 你是個喜歡掌控一切的男人
- Seriously? - You're a man who likes to be in control.
你還有個小型的軍隊在外面站崗
You have a small army standing guard outside.
他們保護你 因為你讓他們相信 他們需要你
They protect you because you've convinced them somehow that they need you,
你卻不明白 你的鎮上出了什麼事?
And you don't know what's going on in your town?
- 你沒告訴他? - 告訴我什麼?
- You didn't tell him? - Tell me what?
你要找的是Santa Muerte
You're looking for santa muerte.
死亡之神
The saint of death.
警長 Omar說的是什麼意思?
Sheriff,what exactly is omar talking about?
任何職業都有自己的保護神
Every job has a patron saint.
警察的是聖猶大 醫生的是大天使拉斐爾
Cops have saint jude, doctors have raphael the archangel.
但要是你是毒販子或者殺手  你會向誰祈禱?
But if you're a drug dealer or a killer, who do you pray to?
死亡之神
The saint of death.
我聽說 要是你 在穿越沙漠到這的路上走失 你就會死
I've learned that crossing the desert to get here, you lose track of the ways you can die.
如果你有親近的人沒有挺過去 怪罪迷信有時候反而會好過些
So if someone close doesn't make it, sometimes it's easier to blame a superstitious figure.
Omar看起來不相信他說的那些
Well,omar doesn't seem like he believes what he's saying.
我沒說他信
I didn't say he believes it.
- 我說的是人們怪罪的那個 - 什麼人?
- I said it's who people are blaming. - What people?
聽著 Santa Muerte出現的越來越頻繁
Look,santa muerte has been coming up more and more.
我遣送回去的非法人員 逮捕的蛇頭
The illegals i send back. The coyotes i arrest.
還有些毒品販子 他們很害怕
Some of the drug traffickers, they're afraid.
害怕這個神?
Afraid of a saint?
我曾經手過一件謀殺案 唯一的證人是一個4歲的女孩子
I handled a homicide once where my only witness was this 4-year-old girl.
她告訴我 她父母是被一條龍殺死的
And she told me her mom and dad got killed by a dragon.
結果是那個兇手穿件綠色的雨衣 戴了只尖頭的帽子
Turns out the bad guy wore a green rain suit with a pointy hood.
在孩子看來 就像條龍
To the kid it looked like a dragon.
所以 要是有很多人都在談論同一個怪物
So when hundreds of people are talking about the same monster,
那麼一定是有事發生了
It's a sure bet something's going on.
他們只是不知道要怎麼稱呼它
They just don't know what to call it.
所以 他們叫他Santa Muerte
So they call it santa muerte.
快點
我只能送到這了
沿著這兒爬過去
我要休息會
一會就跟上來
我早說我們不該放走那個混蛋的
I told you we should have kept that bastard locked up.
我最後再說一次 Boyd 回去巡邏
And i'm telling you for the last time,boyd, go back on patrol.
沒有腐爛 這個受害人剛剛遇害
No decomposition. It's a new victim.
他的矛頭更集中在你身上了 警長
He's becoming more focused on you,sheriff.
警長 能單獨跟你說句嗎?
Sheriff,may i have a word with you?
很明顯 這是私人恩怨
It's clear that this is personal.
- 一直就是的 - 怎麼說?
- It always was. - How's that?
我不知道這幾年有多少這樣的人失蹤了
Look,i have no idea how many of these people have gone missing over the years,
但有一件事很清楚 我是唯一一個在乎的人
but one thing is clear.I'm the only one who seems to give a damn.
所以 這事的矛頭會向著我
That's as personal as it gets for me.
我們就是因為在乎才會站在這
We're here because we care.
我能收集到的 就只有大把的故事和迷信
Well... All i've got is a bunch of stories and superstitions.
要是根本就沒有這麼回事呢?
What if it isn't even happening?
警長 我不知道這已經持續了多久
Sheriff,i can't tell you how long this has been going on,
但現在絕對有事發生了
But something's definitely happening now.
而且從不明疑犯的行為來看 很明顯你觸動到他了
And from the way the unsub is acting, it's obvious that you've touched a nerve.
不管他是誰 我相信你有可能和他談過
Whoever he is,i think you've probably talked to him.
只要有人願意聽 我都會說
I've talked to anyone who will listen.
毒販子 移民 生意人
Drug dealers,immigrants, business owners--
Santa Muerte就是他們中的一個 他感覺到了壓力
Well,one of them is your santa muerte, and he's feeling the pressure.
等我們回到警局  我想查看每一個你做過的詢問
When we get back to the station, i want to go over every single interview you've done.
怎麼做? 我們要找的是誰?
How? Who are we even looking for?
我們有側寫給你和你的警員們
We have a profile to give you and your deputies.
我們要找的人格類型叫做人類捕手
We're searching for a personality type called a human predator--
用傳統的話說就是 獵手
In the classic sense, a hunter.
所有能明確指向他的受害人 都是相對年長 或有某種殘疾
All the victims we've been able to conclusively tie to him have been older or handicapped in some way.
這就說明他會等有人脫離隊伍 尋找最弱勢的一個
This suggests he waits for someone to separate from the pack, looks for the weakest.
像獅子之類的
Like a lion or something.
只是獅子是狩獵食物 這類獵手 獵的是力量
Except a lion hunts food. This type of predator hunts power.
這不是為了滿足需求 所有一切都是為了一個目的
It's not about serving a need, and everything is a means to that end.
我們還認為他是為了削弱受害人的力量 才會迫使他們穿越沙漠
We also believe that he makes his victims run through the desert in order to weaken them.
雖然受害者年長或有殘疾 他也可能 無法在他們最強的狀態下擊倒他們
He may not be capable of taking them on in their strongest state, despite their age or infirmity.
這意味著他有可能在某方面有殘障
This suggests that he's possibly handicapped in some way himself.
但問題不大 或許很小很輕微
Certainly weak, maybe small or even thin.
這樣的製造混亂 然後進行攻擊的行為 會表現在不明嫌犯生活中的所有方面
And an unsub who creates chaos and then attacks typically carries this through to all aspects of his life.
所以他不可能維持一段正常關係
He's unlikely to be in a relationship.
或者在一段關係中 他會是暴力的一方 他很享受他的控制欲
If he is, it's an abusive one. This guy gets off on control.
他會很關注調查進度
He will have tried to stay very close to the investigation.
他很清楚 警長已經開始調查失蹤的非法移民
He's well aware that the sheriff has started looking into the missing illegal immigrants.
你是怎麼看出來的?
How do you know that?
這很有可能是他開始斬首的原因 作為對你的應對對策
It's probably why the decapitations started, as a countermeasure.
他想叫停這個調查
He's trying to throw off the investigation.
這是有組織罪犯的慣用手段
It's typical in an organized offender like this.
Cary Stayner 優勝美地國家公園殺手 故意開車到50英里以外的十字路口
Cary stayner, the yosemite killer, drove more than 50 miles to dump cigarette packs
扔掉他的煙盒和駕照來擺脫自己的嫌疑
And driver's licenses at intersections to throw off suspicion.
從你們已經問過話的 和這些謀殺有關係的人開始著手
Start by looking back at everyone you've talked to in connection with these killings.
和那些熟悉移民的偷渡路線的人開始
We need to start with people who are familiar with the immigrant journey.
例如像誰? 擁護者? 沒人會跟我們說話的 我們已經試過了
Like who? Advocates? None of them will talk to us. I've tried.
蛇頭們希望這個人能消失
Well,the coyotes want this guy caught.
他在損害他們的生意
He's hurting their business.
如果那些擁護者們真的關心那些移民
And if the advocates really care about the immigrants,
他們也想把這個人給揪出來
They're gonna want to find whoever is responsible as well.
有個人或許能幫上忙
There's one guy who could help.
他運營著一個叫Libertad的擴大項目
He runs an outreach program called libertad.
在哪堹鄑鋮鴠L?
Where can we find him?
Clyde 你想帶他們去見Richard Corral嗎?
Clyde,you want to take them over to meet richard corral?
真是我的幸運日啊
My lucky day.
這些FBI探員想跟你談會
These fbi agents want a word with you.
瘸腿 看到嗎?
See the limp?
嗨 寶貝女 我需要你幫我查一個人
Hey,baby girl, i need you to run a check on someone for me.
你有毛病啊 Clyde?
What is wrong with you, clyde?
如果聯邦探員出現在我地盤 我的顧客還會再相信我嗎
None of my clients will trust me if i've got federal agents walking around here.
或許你不應該把你的時間花在 幫非法移民偷渡進國家
Well,maybe you shouldn't spend your time helping illegals sneak into the country.
- 他們只是想要一個更好的生活 - 那他們就應該通過合法途徑
- They only want a better life. - Well,then,they ought to come in the front door.
先生們 改天再吵吧?
Uh,gentlemen, another day?
Corral先生 我們理解你的猶豫
Mr. Corral, we understand your hesitation,
但今天 我們不是為了移民政策來的 是為了謀殺
But we aren't here about immigration, we're here about murder.
你知道前幾天放在警長辦公室門前 那些被砍下的頭嗎?
Do you know anything about the heads that were left in front of the sheriff's station a few days ago?
誰不知道 我的顧客都害怕死了
Everyone does. My clients are terrified.
- 顧客... - 副警長...
- Clients. - Deputy...
昨晚 又有一個人被殺了  一個移民
Another man was murdered last night. An immigrant.
我們需要知道 兇手是怎麼找到他的受害人的
We need to figure out how this man finds his victims.
Ruiz警長說 你比任何人都清楚 非法移民的偷渡路線
Sheriff ruiz said you know more about these people's journey than anyone.
- 是的 - 他們要穿過多少地方?
- Yeah. - How many places are there to cross?
從我們能找到的隧道看來 還有12條隧道沒找到
For every tunnel we find, there's 12 more we don't know about.
當他們穿過了邊境以後呢?
And once they've made it?
蛇頭把檔案都放在他們的卡車上
Runners keep documents in the trunks of their cars.
護照 假社保號 綠卡什麼的
Passports,fake social security numbers, green cards.
這是一盤大生意 特別是在邊境城鎮
It's a big business. Especially in border towns.
你都認識這些蛇頭嗎?
Do you know these runners?
他們老是換人
They change all the time.
如果偷渡的人沒來找你 他們會怎麼辦?
If immigrants don't find you,where do they go?
安全屋 他們本來能在那休息  找到水和食物
Safe houses. It's supposed to be where they can find rest, water,food.
本來能?
Supposed to be?
其實更像是監獄 他們只能一直待在那 直到他們的家人把錢付清給蛇頭
It's more like a prison, until their families can pay off the coyotes.
這些安全屋都在哪?
Where are these safe houses?
你在開玩笑嗎? 它們出現消失得比隧道還快
Are you kidding? They come and go faster than the tunnels.
好的 謝謝你的寶貴時間
Ok. Thank you for your time.
布魯克林一家人被闖入者滅口
警長 我們的地理側寫需要幫助
Sheriff,we could use a hand with the geographical profile.
我們嘗試找出安全屋的地點
We're trying to locate likely safe houses.
你的小隊去遍了整個國家 是吧?
Your team travels all around the country, right?
是的
That's right.
我在兇案組的最後一年 經手了36個謀殺案
My last year in homicide, i handled 36 murders.
我的小隊堣@共20個警探 算一下吧
I was one of 20 detectives in my unit. Do the math.
別問我在那當中 我解決了多少個
Don't ask me how many i solved.
我肯定你已經盡了最大努力了
I'm sure you did the best you could.
就沒有一個地方人們不會互相殘殺嗎?
There really isn't anywhere to go where people aren't killing each other, is there?
可能的安全屋?
Likely safe houses?
即使我們能找到一個
Even if we could find a safe house,
你還真覺得一個剛剛穿過邊境的人 會和我們說話嗎?
You really think someone who just crossed is gonna talk to us?
昨晚的被害人很有可能不是一個人來的
Well,there's a good chance that last night's victim didn't cross alone.
或許有人會掛念他
Someone may be missing him.
如果昨晚才到的非法移民還在安全屋
If last night's illegals are still at safe houses,
我們就能找到他們的偷渡路線 也就知道不明嫌犯的獵殺場了
We can find the route they used and we'll know the unsub's hunting grounds.
安全屋的意義 就在於  它們是個秘密地點
The whole point of a safe house is it's a secret.
如果我能找到它們 我就會把它們搗了
If i'd could find them, i'd shut them down.
好吧 如果那堿O第一站 我們應該從離邊境最近的開始找
All right,if it's a first stop, we should start with homes that are closest to the border.
我能查一下土地契約 但會費點時間
I could pull land deeds. Might take a while.
我們有快一點的方法
We've got something faster.
- Garcia - 長官
- Garcia. - Sir.
我們在搜尋Terlingua的非法移民安全屋
We're looking for illegal immigrant safe houses in terlingua.
有哪些特徵?
What are the parameters?
從有犯罪記錄的房主和租客開始查
Start with homeowners and renters with criminal records.
好的 還有呢
That's a start. Give me more.
Morgan說他們不會總在一個地方 找短期租房
Morgan said they're always moving. Look for homes with short-term leases.
水電用量也會很高
And spikes in utilities.
如果是非法租房 那堨庣q量和用水量會更高
If they're housing illegals, there'll be a higher usage of power and water.
我正在德州所有的公共事業公司
I'm crossing with all texas utility companies.
找到3個地方 已經把地址發到你們手機了
And i have 3. And i just sent the addresses to your phones.
謝謝 Garcia
Thanks,garcia.
如果你們想送給我禮物 像她這樣的就最好不過了
If you're looking for a gift to get me, one of her would be greatly appreciated.
一定不是常規住所
We're pretty sure they broke the mold.
是我
Yeah.
如果你不停的說這違法那違法 我們可查不出什麼東西
You know,we're not going to get very far if you keep arguing about illegals with everyone.
- 這地方以前不是這樣的 - 什麼意思?
- This place used to be different. - How do you mean?
不知道 就是不同
I don't know. Different.
知道了 我們得對各個安全屋各個擊破
Got it,sir. We're gonna split up possible safe houses.
離我們最近的一個離這10分鐘
The closest one to us is 10 minutes from here.
- 他們不會高興見我們的 - 你有手機嗎?
- They ain't gonna be happy to see us. - You got a cell phone?
- 有 - 告訴我號碼
- Yeah. - Give me the number.
副警長 我們在後門 上前敲門
Deputy, we're at the back door. Go ahead and knock.
警察! 開門!
Police! Open up!
漂亮
Nice.
我在大學堿O強衛 (橄欖球堣公礙漱@種)
I played a little strong safety in college.
- 不知道你在說什麼 - FBI 我們有幾個問題要問你
- No idea what that means. - Fbi. We got a few questions for you.
我不會英語
FBI 我們有幾個問題要問你
在這堶?
In here?
你把他們藏在馬棚?
You keep them in a stable?
- 你抓住他? - 好
- You got him? - Yeah.
走
Go.
大家沒事吧?
還有別的人在這嗎?
我媽媽
那個男人把她帶走了
我聽到她哭了
他媽媽
His mother.
Prentiss.
拜託
求你們了...
他強姦我...
別讓我兒子看到我這樣子
Gentry! 我們需要支援和醫療隊!
Gentry! We need backup and medical units!
沒事了 親愛的
Esta bien,querida.
沒事了
Esta bien.
我不會讓他看見你這樣的
謝謝你
現在 你聽我說
Now,you listen to me.
如果你不想和我說話 沒關係 我不介意
If you don't want to talk to me,that's fine. I don't care.
你現在面臨強姦 綁架 持有武器的指控
But you're facing rape, kidnapping, weapons charges,
還有一系列走私和偷渡的聯邦共謀罪名
And numerous counts of federal conspiracy to smuggle and harbor illegal aliens.
這是你能幫自己的最後機會 朋友
This is your last chance to help yourself,my friend.
他看起來一點都不在意
He doesn't look concerned.
因為整個邊境的狀況非常混亂
It's because the whole border situation is chaos.
他被驅逐出境的可能 和入獄的可能差不多
He has as much chance of just getting deported as he does of doing prison time.
我來打幾個電話 看看能不能走點關係
I'll make some calls, see if i can pull some federal strings.
你們走了 誰來幫我們走關係?
Who's gonna pull the strings when you go home?
我們在沙漠中間
我丈夫...
他一直在生病...
...跟不上我們
他不讓我們留下陪他
她丈夫病了 所以落後
Her husband was sick and he stayed behind.
和其他人一樣
Just like the others.
還記得什麼途中的事嗎?
太陽
我看到了太陽
你是說"月亮"
那是晚上 我的寶貝
他是說月亮
El quiere decir la luna.
不 那是太陽
- 他能喝點飲料嗎? - 可以 當然可以
- Can he have soda? - Yeah. Yeah,of course.
來吧 勇敢的孩子 我們去喝飲料
Come on,big man, let's get a soda.
你會找到我丈夫的 對不對?
求你了
Por favor.
我不是一小時以前就讓你回去了嗎
I thought i sent you home an hour ago.
是 但是有點事困擾我
Yeah,uh,something's bugging me.
那個男孩說 他記得偷渡過境的時候 看到了太陽
That young boy says he remembers seeing the sun when he crossed the border.
- 他們是晚上過境的 - 是 我知道 它讓我想起了什麼
- They crossed at night. - Yeah,i know. It got me thinking.
某處舊馬棚邊有一幅很大的壁畫 畫的是太陽
There's a big mural on the side of an old barn. It's of the sun.
- 離這多遠? - 大約15分鐘
- How far out? - About 15 minutes.
- 要一起來嗎? - 好的
- Want to take a ride? - Sure.
我覺著自己從沒來過這地兒
Don't think i've been out this way.
我小時候來這
I used to ride out here when i was a kid.
- 騎馬來的? - 全地形車
- Horses? - Atvs.
從沒坐過
Never been on one of those.
開得時候得小心了 很容易受傷的
Yeah,you gotta be careful with them. You can wreck pretty good.
從小到大我只能騎自行車 還得時刻提防被人偷走
Growing up,all i ever had was a bicycle if i could keep it long enough before it got stolen to ride it.
住城奡N這點不好 對吧
Good reason to hate the city,right?
算是缺點之一
One of them.
那兒 跟那孩子描述的很像
There. It looks a lot like the kid described.
Santa Muerte 和太陽
Santa muerte and the sun.
做的很好 Boyd
That's good police work, boyd.
你覺得FBI的側寫做的怎麼樣?
Hey,what do you think about that profile the fbi gave?
問我的意見?
What do i think?
雖然受害者年長或有殘疾 他也可能 無法在他們最強的狀態下擊倒他們
He may not be capable of taking them on in their strongest state, despite their age or infirmity.
他們說那個男人是個懦夫
They said the guy was a coward.
殺了那麼多人 他就是個混蛋
Anyone kills that many people has gotta be a real bad-ass.
襲擊那些手無縛雞之力的人 在我們那兒 都被叫做膽小鬼
Well,where i come from, preying on people who can't defend themselves makes him a punk-ass.
懦夫
A coward.
把死人頭插在你房子外面 這可不像懦夫
Putting a man's head outside your house hardly seems like a coward.
你腿怎麼了 Boyd?
Something wrong with your leg,boyd?
我十幾歲時腿嚴重骨折過
Yeah,i busted it up pretty bad when i was a teenager.
幾乎沒法跑步
Can't hardly run anymore.
每次臨下雨前都疼得要死
Ooh,it hurts like a bitch every time it's gonna rain now.
這意味著他有可能在某方面有殘障 但問題不大
He's possibly handicapped in some way himself. Certainly weak.
或許很小很輕微
Maybe small or even thin.
我不知道你的腿行動不便
I didn't know you had a bad leg.
- 你對我一無所知 - 你說什麼?
- You didn't know anything about me. - Excuse me?
你從紐約來 然後接管一切
You just came from new york and took over,
只盯著些容易解決的事兒
sticking your nose in things that were going just fine.
你是說那些失蹤案?
You're talking about the missings?
失蹤案 如果那些人一開始
The missing.Now,how could someone be missing
就不該出現在這兒 又怎麼會失蹤呢?
if they ain't supposed to be here in the first damn place?
他們會把一切責任推給Omar
They're gonna blame it all on omar.
我可以擺脫那個賤人和你了
I can get rid of that son of a bitch and you.
為什麼這兒做 Boyd?
Why,boyd?
為什麼? 為什麼不呢?
Why? Why not?
- 你沒法成功的 - 我得試試
- You won't make it. - I gotta try.
我知道
Yeah,i know.
警察都到哪兒去了?
Where are all the deputies?
也許他們發現了另一顆頭
Maybe they found another head.
不會 不然警長會通知我們的 你今早見到她了嗎?
No,the sheriff would have contacted us. Have you heard from her this morning?
沒有 長官 本來也沒指望見到她
No,sir,i wasn't expecting to,though.
JJ 跟我來
Jj,come with me.
收到 第三分隊 隨時更新你的進展
10-4,unit 3. Keep us posted on your progress.
發生什麼了?
What's going on?
警長失蹤了
It's the sheriff. She's missing.
今早她沒出現
She never came in this morning.
巡邏警車也失蹤了 整個部門都在尋找她
Her cruiser's missing,too. The whole department's looking for her.
她對你說過什麼嗎? 她有沒有在跟進什麼?
Did she say anything to you? Was she working on something?
她昨晚比我們先離開
She was gone before we left here last night.
- 去哪兒了? - 我想她是回家了
- Gone where? - I thought she went home.
讓Garcia追蹤她的電話 看看她昨晚 有沒有電話打進來
Have garcia trace her cell phone. See if she had any incoming calls last night.
這是Boyd 上帝啊 我找到她了
This is boyd. Oh,god. I found her.
天 她...請求支援 快!
God,she's all... Just get me some help. Hurry.
- 副警長 - 他做了什麼?
- Deputy. - What he did...
- 是警長嗎? - 沒錯 是她
- It's the sheriff? - Yeah. Yeah,it's her.
這次不一樣 充斥了憤怒
This isn't the same. This is angry.
過度殺戮
And overkill.
作案模式完全不同
It's a completely different m.o.
新的被害者類型
and a new victimology.
他不僅能辨別非法移民  還認得出執法官員?
He goes from impossible to identify illegal immigrants to a law enforcement officer?
側寫中說這男人出於膽小 會挑體弱的人下手
We're profiling a guy who picks on the weakest in a crowd.
我不大瞭解警長  不過她絕不是手無縛雞之力
I didn't know her that well, but weak doesn't seem to fit the sheriff.
- 這不是隨機下手 - 此話怎講?
- It's also not random. - How so?
Omar Morales說過 換作他會這麼做 以發出信息
It's what omar morales said he would do to a body to send a message.
他會這樣子肢解屍體?
He'd tear someone up like that?
這跟他描述的一樣 內臟 頭 舌頭
That's exactly what he said he would do. The evisceration, hand,the tongue.
我和Ruiz在審訊室堮 他說的
He told ruiz and i when we first came into the interrogation room.
- 我們是取證組 - 那邊
- We're the evidence team. - Right there.
- 是她嗎? - 她的一部分
- Is it her? - What's left of her.
車埵酗偵繲?
Is there anything in the car?
沒發現她昨晚去了哪兒
Nothing that would indicate where she was headed last night.
沒筆記 沒日記
There's no notebooks, no log.
肢解方式 和毒販Omar Morales 描述得一模一樣
Her body is mutilated in exactly the way that omar morales,
The drug trafficker, said he would mutilate a body.
側寫指出不明嫌犯和這次的調查關繫緊密
We did profile the unsub would be someone close to the investigation.
可只有Ruiz和我聽到了他的話
But only ruiz and i heard him say it.
所以這都是Omar干的?
So omar looks good for this?
可他幹嗎要殺了全鎮唯一相信 他不是不明嫌犯的人呢?
Except why would he kill the one person in town who didn't think he was the unsub?
Garcia說昨晚九點以後 警長辦公室就沒活動了
Garcia says there's no activity on the sheriff's cell past 9 p.m.
昨晚我們到達時 誰還在局子?
Does anybody remember who was at the station last night when we arrived?
警察局?
The station?
警長被肢解了 和那毒販描述的一模一樣
The sheriff's body was mutilated exactly the way the drug trafficker said he would do it.
- 一模一樣嗎? 舌頭也割了? - 你也聽到了?
- Oh,no,all of it? The tongue,too? - You heard that?
你們和他交談的時候我站在窗戶那兒
Yeah,i was at the window when you were talking to him.
- 牆上有個揚聲器 - 還有誰在那兒?
- There was a speaker on the wall. - Was anybody else there?
Boyd副警長
Yeah,deputy boyd.
Gannon副警長 Boyd副警長在哪兒?
Deputy gannon, where's deputy boyd?
他和Gentry去接他了
Him and gentry went to pick him up.
- 接誰? - Omar Morales
- Pick up who? - Omar morales.
你打算怎麼做?
How do you want to play this?
Boyd!
別幹傻事 Jose
Don't do something stupid,jose.
嘿 別這樣 有話咱好好說
Hey,take it easy. We can work this out.
Boyd! 你他娘的到底在幹啥?
Boyd! What the hell are you doing?
這可不會有用啊
This ain't gonna stick, you know.
Ronny 你都幹了些什麼啊?
Ronny,what did you do?
- 他有槍 - 什麼?
- He had a gun. - What?
他有槍
He had a gun.
Ronny 他沒有
Ronny,he ain't got no gun.
我只能開槍
I had to shoot him.
- 他殺了兩個警察 - 什麼?
- He killed two cops. - What?
- Gentry - Gentry 我是Prentiss探員
- Gentry. - Gentry,this is agent prentiss.
如果他在你旁邊 別說話
If he's near you, please don't say anything.
我們認為Boyd副警長就是不明嫌犯
We think the unsub may be deputy boyd.
Gentry 你在聽嗎?
Gentry,are you there?
- Reid JJ 待在這 保持警惕 - 好的
- Reid,jj,stay out here and stay alert. - Yeah.
是Gentry
It's gentry.
你覺得這合理嗎?
Does this look legit to you?
Omar是被散彈獵槍打中的 Gentry只有把手槍
Omar took shotgun hits. Gentry only has a pistol.
Omar兩隻手上也都沒有火藥殘餘
There's no powder residue on omar's hands,either.
哦 我的天 萬一是他接的電話呢?
Oh,my god. What if he heard me?
- Gannon Boyd會去哪? - 不知道
- Gannon, where would boyd go? - I don't know.
沒時間包庇他了  他殺了你們的頭還有Gentry
This is no time to be covering up. He killed your boss and gentry.
我沒包庇他 我真不知道  我不是很瞭解他 沒人瞭解
I'm not covering. I don't know the guy that well. No one does.
他總是獨來獨往
He's a loner.
- 大人 - Garcia  Boyd副警長 就是不明嫌犯 他有警用無線電
- My liege. - Garcia,deputy boyd is our unsub. He has a police radio.
- 你能追蹤到嗎? - 可以 單位號是多少?
- Can you track it? - Yeah. What's his unit number?
打電話給警長辦公室  問調度員序列號
Call the sheriff's station. Get the serial numbers from the dispatcher.
好 我再打給你
Ok,i'll get back to you.
- 我們側寫他是個獵人 - 現在是獵物了
- We profiled him as a hunter. - Well, now he's the hunted.
他一定會去讓他有安全感的地方
He'll go someplace he feels safe.
- 他能控制的地方 - 回家?
- Someplace he knows he can control. - Home?
不會 應該是事先設計好的地方
No,i think a preplanned location.
長官 發現他了 他在往北的方向
Sir,i've got him. He's heading northbound.
- 州際公路? - 不是  他根本沒開上路 他在沙漠媔}
- Interstate? - No,he is not on a road at all. He's driving through the desert.
- 繼續追蹤 Garcia - 他想逃跑
- Keep tracking him,garcia. - He's running.
肯定不是跑回家  他住在城外西邊的一部拖車
Not home for sure. He lives in a trailer out west of town.
那他是要跑去哪?
So where's he running to?
Morgan Prentiss Reid 副警長 你帶他們去拖車 看能發現點什麼
Morgan,prentiss,reid-- deputy, you take them to his house, see what you can find.
把你無線電給我
I need your radio.
- 你要怎麼做? - 不讓他閒著
- What are you gonna do? - Keep him busy.
副警長Boyd  我是FBI的Hotchner探員
Deputy boyd, this is agent hotchner with the fbi.
我知道你能聽到我 你無處可逃
I know you can hear me. You have no place to go.
這沙漠是我的地盤
This is my desert.
你以為能把我找出來麼 哼 試試吧
You think you can find me out here, yeah,well,come on out.
自以為了不起的混蛋
Cocky little bastard.
問題是他說得沒錯  我們對這沙漠一無所知
The trouble is he's right. We don't know anything about this desert.
也許他們能發現點線索
Hope they can find something.
哦 天啊
Oh,god.
看來我們真是找對地方了
Well,we're definitely in the right place.
和平常一樣呼吸就好了  嗅覺是最弱的感官知覺
Just breathe through your nose like normal. Smell is the weakest sense.
過個幾分鐘 你就聞不出什麼了
In a few more minutes, you won't even notice it.
那味覺呢?
What about the taste?
那是你自己想的
I think that's in your head.
好 分頭找吧 看看這傢伙要去哪
All right,spread out. Let's find out where this guy's headed here.
Boyd 沒必要讓這一切變得更糟的
Boyd,this doesn't have to end any worse than it already is.
- 怎麼說? - 你自首 我會和法官說你很合作
- Is that right? - Turn yourself in. I'll tell the judge you cooperated.
這兒是德克薩斯 探員  你以為法官在能判人死刑時
This is texas,agent.You think the judge gives a damn
還會在乎他有沒有合作嗎?
whether or not someone cooperated when he's handing out the death penalty?
別理解錯了
Now,don't get me wrong.
我也會用一樣的方式結束這一切
I wouldn't have it any other way.
那是對付我這種人唯一的方式
That's the only way to deal with someone like me.
他會自殺嗎?
Think he's suicidal?
- 要不就是嚇唬人 - 北邊有什麼東西?
- Or he's bluffing. - What's north of here?
- 空空如也 - 他一點也不驚慌
- A whole lot of nothing. - He's not panicking.
那兒一定有什麼東西吸引著他
There's something out there, and he's headed for it.
哦 天哪 我發現那氣味是哪來的了
Oh,god. I found where the source of that smell is coming from.
哦 我的天
Oh,my god.
這就是他砍人頭的地方了
Well,this is where he decapitated them.
夥計們 來看這個
Guys,come look at this.
我一直等著嗅覺失靈呢 Reid
I'm ready for that smell weakness to kick in anytime,reid.
你們聽 "金色收穫穀物供給倉庫
Listen."golden harvest grain and feed
今天又一次遭受了因組長Fred Boyd 死亡而起的控制權之爭"
"suffered another setback today in a ruling over the death of foreman fred boyd."
Boyd死了 其子Ronald活了下來
"boyd survived by his son ronald."
上次那個受害人的孩子不是說 在路上看到了太陽嗎?
Didn't the last victim's child say that he saw the sun when he crossed?
- 是有 - 金色收穫 就在城外北邊
- Yeah. - Golden harvest, that's out north of town.
長官 我--我追蹤不到他了  訊號消失了
Sir,i--i lost him. The signal's gone.
他弄壞了無線電
He smashed the radio.
Garcia 給我張信號 最後出現的衛星照片
Garcia,i need a satellite photo of the last place that the signal showed.
那堣@定有什麼是地圖上沒顯示的
There's something out there that's not on the map.
是 長官 我正在弄
Yes,sir,i'm already working on that.
去北邊
Let's head north.
Hotch 城北有一個叫金色收穫的 很舊的穀物供給倉庫
Hotch,there's an old grain and feed barn north of town called golden harvest.
Boyd的父親是在那堻Q殺害的
Boyd's father was killed there.
Garcia正在查找確切地點
Garcia's searching for an exact address right now.
- 好 我們到那碰頭 - 這都是受害人
- Ok,right. We'll see you there. - His victims.
Reid 你在這留守現場好吧?
Reid,i want you to stay with the crime scene, all right?
我打電話給州里的和當地的同事
I'll call the state and local bureau offices.
他們會馬上趕過來的
They'll be here as soon as they can.
別在車媔}槍
Try not to shoot that inside the car.
- 你意思是別震聾你? - 對
- You mean try not to deafen you? - Exactly.
那是他的車
There's his vehicle.
你走側門 我從前門入
You take the side door. I'll take the front.
注意上面的窗戶
Watch the windows up top.
- 你能開槍嗎? - 我什麼都看不見
- Do you have a shot? - I can't see anything.
- Prentiss 當心! - 交給我 交給我
- Prentiss,look out! - I got him,i got him.
你沒事吧?
You all right?
- 沒事 - 有事!
- Yeah. - No!
你是不是瘋了? 我耳膜都震破了
Are you out of your mind? You blew out my eardrum.
那你想讓我怎麼辦?  他衝著我們就過來了
What did you want me to do? He was coming right at us.
我說了我能搞定的
I told you i had him.
他都朝我們開槍了 Emily
He was shooting at us, emily.
那你至少能提醒我下吧
Well,you could have given me a heads-up.
這可是把上了膛的mp-5衝鋒鎗和 往我們亂掃的瘋子啊? 行了
The loaded mp-5 and the lunatic shooting at us wasn't enough? Come on.
上邊派過來一個犯罪現場小組了
The state's sending out a crime scene team.
沒有失蹤人口的報告 要確認屍體身份很難
It's going to be hard to identify the bodies with out missing persons reports.
我聯繫了那個安排移民的 Richard Corral
I called that advocate, richard corral.
他正在聯繫有親人失蹤的人家
He's contacting families with missing relatives.
他會試著拿到些DNA
He's gonna try and get some dna.
那應該能好點
That'll help.
這都亂套了
This is a mess.
沒有Ruiz警長會更亂的  還是會有人被砍頭
It would have been a bigger mess without sheriff ruiz, and it would still be happening.
她有什麼家人嗎?
Did she have any family?
我已經讓Garcia在查了
I already have garcia checking into it.
我會給布魯克林的兇殺組打電話 和我認識的幾個人說說
I'm going to call brooklyn homicide, talk to some of the guys i know there.
- 給她頒發獎章 - 太好了
- They'll honor her shield. - That's good.
從紐約警局出來的探長會很高興的
An ex-nypd detective would like that.
我們回去吧
Let's go home.
"許多人對於什麼是真正的幸福 都有著錯誤的觀念"
"many persons have the wrong idea "of what constitutes true happiness.
"真正的幸福不是自我滿足 而是忠實地為值得的目標自我奉獻"
"it is not attained through self-gratification but through fidelity to a worthy purpose."
海倫·凱勒  (美國聾盲女作家 慈善家 教育家)
Helen keller.
犯罪心理 第五季 第19集
== 結束 ==
Criminal Minds Season05 Episode19 Rite of Passage